Nicholas Bukdahl

Game and level designer

Copenhagen, Denmark +45 61 33 24 01 nicholasbukdahl@outlook.com linkedin.com/in/nicholasbukdahl nicholasbukdahl.com



PROFILE

To create truly fun and engaging gameplay, I challenge established design principals, break the rules and bend them to my advantage. I keep my skills up-to-date by continuing to study, create, fail and learn from my experiences, as I strive to stay innovative with my designs. I am a super social team-player that has a burning passion for creating games, sharing ideas and making friendships.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Language / Software	Years' experience	Skill level
C#	2	Intermediate
Unity3D	4	Expert
SourceTree / SVN	2	Proficient
Photoshop	6	Proficient

WORK EXPERIENCE

2016 - now | Game Designer | NapNok Games

Working with various unreleased and top-secret projects, some of which are currently unannounced.



- Game & level designer on Sinking Feeling PlayStation VR (in development).
- Ownership of game design and gameplay features on unannounced project.
- Worked in a cross-disciplinary and agile workflow with teams of 6 40 people.

2012 – 2016 | Senior Sales Associate | GameStop



Responsible for selling and providing customer service to a wide range of customers in a very competitive market.

- Advised customers on purchases, trades and pre-orders.
- Met and exceeded weekly KPI numbers.
- Member of award winning Best Sales Team Denmark 2015.

2015 - 2015 | LEVEL DESIGNER | DADIU (Internship)

Member of the lead team for the game *Spoken* with responsibility for level design and level implementation in Unity.



- Agile development
- Level balance based on QA testing and feedback.
- Minor AI scripting & gameplay programming (C#).
- Game released on App Store and Google Play.
- Nominated for <u>Spilprisen 2016</u> in category Best Showcase.

EDUCATION

2014 - 2016 | MSc. Medialogy with specialisation in Games at Aalborg University, Denmark

The Master's has allowed me to focus on the science of games and to have a corporate collaboration with LEGO on exploring the free-build experiences. The project gave me practical experience with research and development of a product, which I applied when interning at DADIU.

Here I worked as a level designer, part of a team of 16, to develop a game created in Unity. I was responsible for the development, implementation and balancing of levels based on feedback from user tests. The game was released and nominated for *Spilprisen 2016* in the category *Best Showcase*. The internship allowed me to use my experience from working in large teams and cross-disciplinary communication skills that I developed as a medialogist.

2011 - 2014 | BSc. Medialogy at Aalborg University, Denmark

During my Bachelor's I have obtained a broad understanding of media technology and media science on both a theoretical and practical level with the interest of specializing in the science of games.

This became especially relevant during my 5th semester when I worked with game- and level design in an asymmetrical multiplayer game titled *The Eye of Sauron*. A player would play as the Eye using an Oculus Rift, with the objective to eliminate the hobbits (other players) before they destroyed the Eye.

My bachelor project titled *Augmentation of Board Games Using Smartphones* focused on social presence in board games and if there was a difference when playing a digital augmented version versus a traditional board game. The project report was developed into a paper and published at HCI International 2015.

VOLUNTEER

2015 – 2017 | Organizer | Nordic Game Jam

Member of core-organizer team with responsibility for the infodesk, through which over 900 participants were checked in.



- Worked with location partner to ensure network stability.
- Verified presentation rooms and their technical specifications.

2012 - 2014 | Board Member | Student Society at Aalborg University Esbjerg

The student society in Esbjerg is only a small group of people. However, these are some of the most eager people to do their best in creating events for students and speaking on their behalf at campus meetings.



LANGUAGES

Danish Native

English Professional working proficiency